<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mdneuzerling</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mdneuzerling</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>useR: Getting started with R and Docker</title>
      <link>/post/user-getting-started-with-r-and-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/user-getting-started-with-r-and-docker/</guid>
      <description>Docker glossary Running docker images Rocker R hello world Playing with the hello-world image A note on security Managing Docker without leaving R  Docker on AWS And that’s it!   These are my notes for the super helpful tutorial given by Elizabeth Stark on the first day of the UseR 2018 conference. This was an introduction to Docker for R users who have no prior experience with Docker (which was me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scraping wine colours with R</title>
      <link>/post/scraping-wine-colours-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/scraping-wine-colours-with-r/</guid>
      <description>My knowledge of wine covers three facts:
I like red wine. I do not like white wine. I love wine data.  I came across a great collection of around 130,000 wine reviews, each a paragraph long, on Kaggle. This is juicy stuff, and I can’t wait to dig into it with some text analysis, or maybe build some sort of markov chain or neural network that generates new wine reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy App 1</title>
      <link>/itemized/item1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/itemized/item1/</guid>
      <description> App 1 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy App 2</title>
      <link>/itemized/item2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/itemized/item2/</guid>
      <description> App 2 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy App 3</title>
      <link>/itemized/item3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/itemized/item3/</guid>
      <description> App 3 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fancy App 4</title>
      <link>/itemized/item4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/itemized/item4/</guid>
      <description> App 4 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using R to send an Outlook email with an inline image</title>
      <link>/post/using-r-to-send-an-outlook-email-with-an-inline-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/using-r-to-send-an-outlook-email-with-an-inline-image/</guid>
      <description>If you work in a corporate environment, there’s a good chance you’re using Microsoft Office. I wanted to set up a way to email tables and plots from R using Outlook. Sending an email is simple enough with the RDCOMClient library, but inserting a plot inline—rather than as an attachment—took a little bit of working out. I’m sharing my code here in case anyone else wants to do something similar. The trick is to save your plot as an image with a temporary file, attach it to the email, and then insert it inline using a cid (Content-ID).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We started a maths and stats society at our university, and everyone loves it</title>
      <link>/post/we-started-a-maths-and-stats-society-at-our-university-and-everyone-loves-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/we-started-a-maths-and-stats-society-at-our-university-and-everyone-loves-it/</guid>
      <description>Last year an honours student noticed something missing in mathematics and statistics at La Trobe University. She saw that there was no society at the university to cultivate an interest in mathematics. There were no social events to help the undergraduate students get to know one another. And there was very little in the way of extracurricular lectures for students without several years of mathematical study already under their belt. So she started the Mathematics and Statistics Society at La Trobe University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My fourth Australasian Combinatorics Conference</title>
      <link>/post/my-fourth-australasian-combinatorics-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/my-fourth-australasian-combinatorics-conference/</guid>
      <description>My first maths conference was The 36th Australasian Conference on Combinatorial Mathematics and Combinatorial Computing. I had just finished my honours thesis, Generalising the Clique-Coclique Bound, and I had travelled to Sydney to present my results to a room full of people much smarter than me.
I’m no longer working in graph theory or finite geometry, but every year since 2012 I have attended the ACCMCC. I keep up to date with the research, and I maintain contact with some of the best mathematicians I’ve ever met.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>